Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989 AIS.1982.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records
1966-1989
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Service Employees International Union. Local 585 (Blawnox, Pa.)
AIS.1982.14
214.2 Linear Feet (174 boxes)
Service Employees International Union (SEIU) Local 585 was chartered in 1969 and represented health care employees, nonprofessional school district workers, and county civil servants in western Pennsylvania until 2002 when the local was disbanded. This collection contains information about Local 585 members and contract negotiations, typically organized by employer name.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged into two series. The first is comprised of materials from the initial collection accession, which were arranged sometime in the 1990s. The second series contains all of the records added to the collection since 1982 and have not yet been more formally arranged.
Series I. Chapter Files: Education
Series II. Collection Additions
History
Service Employees International Union (SEIU) Local 585 was chartered in 1969 after the passing of Pennsylvania Public Employees Act, Act 195, which established the right for public employees to organize and bargain collectively. The local represented three broad categories of workers in the Pittsburgh area: health care employees, nonprofessional school district workers, and county civil servants. In 1973, Rosemary Trump was elected president and under her tenure Local 585 grew to represent 15,000 workers throughout western Pennsylvania, becoming the second largest union in the region. While the number of employees in manufacturing unions declined, the number of employees in the service industry was on the rise and Local 585 was one of the few Pittsburgh area unions to increase its membership during the 1990s. In 1999, the local incorporated SEIU Local 29 which was also operating in Pittsburgh.
The 2000 election saw President Trump narrowly lose to newcomer Jim Neville, who was later removed by the international union under allegations that he violated the union's constitution. In March 2001, Local 585 was placed under the trusteeship of a member of SEIU District 925, who was then replaced that November by a trustee from Local 1199 Upstate in New York. In 2002, Local 585 was disbanded and its members were disbursed among three other industry specific SEIU locals: Local 668, government workers; Division 29/Local 47, commercial janitors and building maintenance services workers; and Local 1199P, health care workers.
Previous Citation
Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989, AIS.1982.14, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Accruals
Additional material received from SEIU #585 in 1989; Rosemary Trump donated material in 2003.
Acquisition Information
Gift of SEIU 585 in 1982.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Related Material
Rosemary Trump Papers, 1950-2005, AIS.2005.04, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Service Employees International Union Local 29 Records, 1967-1990, AIS.1995.09, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Service Employees International Union Local 668 (Pennsylvania Social Services Union) Records, 1970s-1990s, AIS.1981.09, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains contract negotiation information, grievances, member and seniority lists, and dues information from the various employers of members of Service Employees International Union Local 585. Also included are files regarding organization efforts in western Pennsylvania, as well as interunion rivalries and raids by other unions, such as the Teamsters, National Education Association and the Pennsylvania State Education Association. Executive board and membership meeting minutes from the 1970s are also present.
Correspondence; Pittsburgh (Pa.); Blawnox (Pa.); Grievance arbitration -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Collective labor agreements -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Service industries workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Cleaning personnel -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Labor; Labor unions -- Political activity -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Service Employees International Union. Local 585 (Blawnox, Pa.); Democratic Party (Pa.); Service Employees International Union; Trump, Rosemary T.
- Chapter Files: Education, I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series includes files relating to chapters of SEIU Local 585 at educational institutions and represents the initial collection donation in 1982. The first portion of the series lists public school districts alphabetically by district name. The second portion lists colleges and universities alphabetically by school name. These files include information on organization efforts, contract negotiations and membership.
  - School Districts, 1.
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Organization, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Negotiations, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Dues Check-Off Authorizations, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Negotiations, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Wilbur Shea Grievance, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Membership Lists, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Membership Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Contract, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Contract, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Working Copy of Negotiations Contract, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Contract, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Members/School Board Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Officers Elections, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Unemployment, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Albert Gallatin School District - Contract, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Organization, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Mediation Notices, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Membership Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - School Board Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Salary Schedules, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Contract, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Contract, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Organization: Secretaries, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - School Board Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Political Action, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Contract, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - Contract, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Allegheny Valley School District - John Seronka Grievance, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Organization, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Scheduling Grievances, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Membership Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Contract, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Seniority/Salary List, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Membership Correspondence/Notices, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - School Board Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Negotiations, January-July 1975 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Negotiations, July 24-October 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Strike, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Inter-Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Strikes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Negotiations/Contract, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Cessna Grievance, January-April 23, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Cessna Grievance, April 28, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Inter-Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Key Management Cafeteria Takeover, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Grievances, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Grievances, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Contract, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Negotiations/Grievances, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Personnel/Seniority Lists, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Contract: Cafeteria, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Contract: Custodial, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Negotiations, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Subcontracting: Custodial, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Grievances/Seniority, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Inter-Union: PSEA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Grievance, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Apollo-Ridge School District - Negotiations/Unfair Labor Practice Charge, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Armstrong School District - Pre-Union Period, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Armstrong School District - Salary List, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Armstrong School District - Teachers Strikers, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Armstrong School District - Grievances/Negotiations, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Armstrong School District - Dues/Death Gratuities, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Armstrong School District - Contract, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization, March-April 23, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization, April 24-May 1970 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations/Pay Board, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Armstrong School District - Sex Discrimination Suit, February-May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Armstrong School District - Sex Discrimination Suit, July 16, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Armstrong School District - Sex Discrimination Suit, July 18-20, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Armstrong School District - Cafeteria Wages/Seniority, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Armstrong School District - Grievances/Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Armstrong School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Armstrong School District - Enrollment/Cafeteria, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Armstrong School District - Cafeteria Contract, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization/Grievances/Negotiations, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Armstrong School District - Dues/Death Benefits (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Armstrong School District - Wages/Fringes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Armstrong School District - Teacher Negotiations, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Armstrong School District - Unfair Labor Practices, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Armstrong School District - Unfair Labor Practices, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization/Negotiations, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Armstrong School District - Proposed Contract, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Armstrong School District - Proposed Contract, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Armstrong School District - Teachers' Contracts, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations/Grievances, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Armstrong School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Armstrong School District - Sex Discrimination Case, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Armstrong School District - Membership Correspondence, 1972-April 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Armstrong School District - Membership Correspondence, July-December 1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Armstrong School District - School Board Correspondence, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Armstrong School District - Teachers' Contract, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Armstrong School District - Cafeteria Contract, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Armstrong School District - Clerical Contract, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Armstrong School District - Teacher Contract, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization/Negotiations: Secretaries, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Armstrong School District - Membership Correspondence, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Armstrong School District - Secretary Association Contract, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Armstrong School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Clerical, February-June 1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Clerical, July-August 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Clerical, September 1974-January 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations/Strike: Clerical, February-March 1975 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Armstrong School District - Grievance, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization: Teacher Aides, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Armstrong School District - Dues, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Teacher Aides, July-October 1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Teacher Aides, December 1976 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Teacher Aides, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Armstrong School District - Unit Clarification, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Armstrong School District - Secretaries' Strike, February 10-24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Armstrong School District - Secretaries' Strike, February 25-March 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Armstrong School District - Secretaries' Strike, March 11, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Armstrong School District - Membership/Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Armstrong School District - NEA Minutes, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Armstrong School District - Grievances, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Armstrong School District - Membership Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Armstrong School District - Grievances/Issues, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Custodial, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Armstrong School District - Retirement Board Election, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Armstrong School District - Officer Elections/Membership Meetings, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Armstrong School District - Unfair Labor Practices, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization: Clerical, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Armstrong School District - Grievances, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Armstrong School District - School Board, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Armstrong School District - Membership Status, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Armstrong School District - Inter-Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Armstrong School District - Grievances/Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Armstrong School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Armstrong School District - Clerical Unit Minutes, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Armstrong School District - Contract: Maintenance, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Armstrong School District - Salary List: Maintenance, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Armstrong School District - Contract: Maintenance, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Clerical, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Maintenance, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization: Teacher Aides, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Teacher Aides, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Armstrong School District - Organization/Negotiations: Teacher Aides, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Armstrong School District - Contracts: Teacher Aides, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Teacher Aides, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Armstrong School District - Milligan Grievance, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Armstrong School District - Negotiations: Clerical, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Armstrong School District - Contracts, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Auella School District - Organization, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Auella School District - Negotiations/Grievances, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Auella School District - Organization, February-July 1977 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Auella School District - Organization, September-October 1977 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Auella School District - Classification: Parker & Caldwell, 1978-January 1979 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Auella School District - Classification: Parker & Caldwell, February 1979 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Auella School District - Classification: Parker & Caldwell, March-April 2, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Auella School District - Classification: Parker & Caldwell, April 3-30, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Auella School District - Proposed Contract, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Auella School District - Negotiations, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Auella School District - Parker and Caldwell PLRB Case, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Auella School District - Contract, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Auella School District - Parker & Caldwell PLRB Cases, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Auella School District - Parker & Caldwell PLRB Cases, January-February 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Auella School District - Parker & Caldwell PLRB Cases, March 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Auella School District - Parker & Caldwell PLRB Cases, April-August 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Auella School District - Parker & Caldwell PLRB Cases, October-November 22, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Auella School District - Parker & Caldwell PLRB Cases, November 29, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Avonworth School District - Organization, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Avonworth School District - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Avonworth School District - Contracts, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Avonworth School District - Negotiations/Grievances, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Avonworth School District - Dues, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Avonworth School District - Wage Freeze Board, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Avonworth School District - Working Conditions, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Avonworth School District - Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Avonworth School District - Contracts, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Avonworth School District - Seniority Lists, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Avonworth School District - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Avonworth School District - Contracts, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Avonworth School District - Dues, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Avonworth School District - Negotiations/Grievances, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Bentworth School District - Organization, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bentworth School District - Organization, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Bentworth School District - Negotiations/Grievances, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Bentworth School District - Dues, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Bentworth School District - Custodial Duties, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Bentworth School District - Proposed Contract, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Bentworth School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Bentworth School District - Organization: Cafeteria, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Bentworth School District - Chapter Meetings, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Bentworth School District - Grievances/Issues, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Bentworth School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bentworth School District - Contracts: Cafeteria & Teacher Aides, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bentworth School District - Contract: Custodians, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Bentworth School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Bentworth School District - Grievances, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Bentworth School District - Dues, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Bentworth School District - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Bentworth School District - Reho Grievance, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Bentworth School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Bentworth School District - Contracts: Custodians, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Bentworth School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Bethel Park School District - Contract: Custodians, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Bethel Park School District - Dues, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Bethel Park School District - Factionalism, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Bethel Park School District - Organization/Negotiations, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Bethel Park School District - Grievances/Meet & Discuss (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Bethel Park School District - Dues, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Bethel Park School District - Organization: Cafeteria (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Bethel Park School District - Negotiations, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Bethel Park School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Bethel Park School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Bethel Park School District - Cafeteria Rules, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Bethel Park School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Bethel Park School District - Membership/Dues, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Bethel Park School District - Wildcat Strike: Cafeteria, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Bethel Park School District - Membership Meetings/Officers Election, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 58)